No Honor. No Respect. No Remorse.
The Young Americans is a thriller, drama, crime film directed by Danny Cannon.
Experienced New York Police Detective John Harris is sent to London to help a local task force
investigate a series of gangster killings organized by a new player in town, an American.
With the help of a young teen wronged by gangsters, Harris navigates London's seedy,
drug-fuelled underworld in order to take down its new criminal empire.
John Harris, played by Harvey Keitel.
Edward Foster, played by Iain Glen.
Richard Donnelly, played by John Wood.
Sidney Callow, played by Terence Rigby.
Jack Doyle, played by Keith Allen.
Christian O'Neill, played by Craig Kelly.
The Young Americans is a 1993 crime drama film directed
by Danny Cannon in his directorial debut.
The film explores themes of london, england, police,
policeman, rave culture, club life.
The tone is emotional and intense.